Hello everyone
We are the guests of the fourth season of "Half-Mature Lovers"
I am Hou Chengjie
Hello everyone
I am Liang Tian
I am Hu Yunting
Oh, what?
Hello everyone
I am Zheng Weiying
My name is Luo Junfan
I'm not important, it's okay
But indeed, it's been a long time since we last met.
I think we should all chat some more.
About our recent situations.
What have you been up to?
How's it going?
I've been on winter break.
And then
Winter break.
You're like an ant moving a frog.
That's awesome.
I've been on break for over two months.
So I hope to start working soon like you all.
Can start working.
Are you on winter break or unemployed?
Clarify that.
Okay, I'll ask the questions.
You ask the questions.
So, Ms. Liang Tian,
After the show,
What did you do?
Being myself.
That's great.
No.
It was the New Year.
Then I went home.
Chen and I are both from Shenyang.
We arranged to have a meal together.
We had a small barbecue.
And one day we had afternoon tea.
It was great.
Finished ordering
Sitting and chatting
So the upcoming program
Do you have any connections with Brother Chen?
No
Everyone, look forward to it
Maybe there's a connection with Brother Chen
He is my brother
What's going on with you guys?
Okay
I miss everyone too
Yes
Went back to Taiwan for the New Year
Then after a long period
Started working after coming back
But haven't had time to see everyone yet
He doesn't even have time to reply to my messages
I've been very busy lately
Working nine to five every day
Working diligently
You're living the life Xiao Hou dreams of
So envious of you
Our company is saturated
I'll just talk about my life
At home, it's mainly four words
Turn over a new leaf
Everyone
Why are you feeling guilty?
It's just that my knees have gravity
Knees
Where is Kaka (Zheng Weiying)?
Do you miss the little house?
I miss it a lot.
I miss it a lot too.
I think I cherish it more than I miss it.
There will always be someone in the little house.
So you never feel lonely.
It's like having someone to keep you company.
Not replying to messages.
Really.
But seeing your messages
makes me very happy.
Everyone tags him in the group, but he doesn't reply.
He ignores it.
Actually, what I miss the most is being in the little house
having meals with everyone.
That period of time.
That long dining table.
Yes, the long dining table.
When everyone sat together at it.
I felt very warm.
But don't say I missed a meal
because of you.
Can you call Zheng Weiying for me?
I
Kaka (Zheng Weiying)
Because she just picked up her chopsticks
and you called her out.
It's been a long time since we last met.
We've talked so much.
But our main task today is
to watch together with everyone.
So next, let's watch together
the third episode of the fourth season of "Half-Mature Lovers."
Finally, we can watch it.
Looking forward to it.
Alright
It's time for my execution scene.
I woke up.
Finally, I can enjoy it.
No
This part of mine is very funny.
Come see how I go on a date.
Washing hands so quickly
afraid of missing a second.
My brother rubbed his hands so hard that sparks flew.
Ignite the passion within his instincts
Very skilled
This post-production teacher
Post-production teacher
Really skilled
The subtitle team deserves a reward
So sweet
This is so harmonious
I'll go back and block you on WeChat
You are wasting people's time
Old Hu, cover me.
Cover me.
You won't talk to me because of this kind of person.
He is very sweet
Did he see Xiao Hou bring food?
So he knows he needs to bring food
He got inspired
Brother, you're awesome.
I will raise a big flag and light signs for my brother.
Understands me
Understands me too well
Thank you, post-production teacher
So this is what other people's dates are like
This is so blissful
Wozi (Ren Jiabi)
Jun Ji-hyun
So this is what she's like
So beautiful
The atmosphere here is so nice
Sister "kills" me
Really so beautiful
This look in the eyes
Xiao Hou's eyes are so big
I just realized eyes can open this wide
Why are you blinking so much
Are you that nervous
Nervous
You listen to her so seriously
Super serious
His eyes
Open your eyes a bit wider
None of them are pushovers.
You must have felt great at that moment.
Why don't you show it then?
Xiao Hou
Hou Chengjie
I didn't know I was with a big shot
My apologies
I am observing
Because Xiao Hou went
to each of our dates
Yes
Then you can see
whether he is chatting with me
or making a cake for you
Xiao Hou's feeling
that rhythm is where he stops
but with Wo Wo (Ren Jiabi) it's that kind
he is moving forward little by little
Yes
when he talks to others
he actually just asks a question
then answers one here and it's over
he asks one and answers one
then he keeps digging deeper
he just says
psychologically speaking
I just want to know a little more
Yes
I think this is really great
But actually, earlier
I think Kaka's (Zheng Weiying) cake setup
is really cute
you would honestly say
it's like a scene from an idol drama
actually, you are the voice of many comments
really
I think during your date
you were especially generous
actually, you see so many people here
but you express this state
making everyone feel comfortable
really?
it's happy
I think everyone should be happy
especially in comparison
I think I didn't do well either.
Suddenly I felt
But I had no choice.
I was very embarrassed at that time.
But I think
Kaka (Zheng Weiying)'s way of handling it was particularly good.
No
It's because I pay more attention to my own feelings.
I didn't mean to say
I must take care of someone.
I want to say
I was the one leading this date.
I should start from my own ideas.
as the central point.
This feeling
Actually, it's better for you to do it this way.
Yes
I have learned.
A new war has started again.
Is there another civilization competition?
No.
I am very harmonious.
Very harmonious.
That day I felt
I started to realize here
I realized what Old Su meant.
Old Su came over to tell you.
I made her wear those glasses.
I really
I take back what I said earlier
about you having a strong sense of boundaries
turns out you have some tactics too
I
What
disappointed
Yes, it was strange that day
Yes, because I wanted to come back and apologize quickly
wanted to apologize
That's true
I was actually very sad at that time
but I felt
I didn't know what was happening at that time
Yes
but I still hoped
to be a bit happier in the room
So at that time, each of us really
I heard you
Now I know
Yes
That's actually how it is
When everyone is happy
I don't want to be particularly unhappy
Look who
Brother
Look who, brother
Let me guess
But this seems pretty obvious
Right
Pretty obvious
Yes
My brother is still slow, my brother
He definitely doesn't know what happened
Because this happened after he left
He wants to say I wasn't late
He thinks so himself
Yes
I'm sorry
Lao Luo
I didn't know
This must be made clear
You're not late
Very similar
Actually, we have great chemistry
This is definitely fate
Confidence
Confident men are the most handsome
Really anxious
It must be
I was a bit speechless at that time.
This is too funny
I, Ms. Wozi (Ren Jiabi)
Alright, Wowo (Ren Jiabi)
It was a cover-up
I understand now
She suddenly ran over and said she wanted to make breakfast
Looks good
The best viewing spot is to watch you two
What should we do
This is also good
I have done these things
This is well shot
Good technique
She is a very rational girl.
Very wise.
Very steady.
What the heck
The main thing is this is a reverse selection
It's the girl who goes to knock on the door
You handled this very well.
This was handled very well.
Yes, very good.
I really think this interaction made me
remind me
It's really a mature and semi-mature love.
Because you handled it so well.
This is quite sweet.
Why are you always shipping?
This is sweet, that is sweet too.
So that's how it is.
I think Xia (Xia Mengting) wants something.
She will give others what she wants.
This is a very good quality of hers.
What do you mean?
I went to invite him.
You're so brave, Brother.
Brother.
Teacher Hou
Great
Actually, this is also for me
You are also someone who has let go of their mental burdens.
Yes.
You wouldn't stay behind.
To have more opportunities with her.
He did this during a life-and-death situation.
I really got goosebumps.
This is great
Such a sweet smile
Let's play together
So satisfying
Really addictive
Perfect
I feel healed by you
I truly feel healed by you
That's great
It's still very beautiful
Quick and decisive
Take it down
It's like this
Guozi (Ren Jiabi) is so cute
Victory and defeat are common in warfare.
You feel relieved.
Yes, relieved.
You go out and invite Teacher Liang (Liang Tian)
Yes
I was confused again
Brother Luo
I'm going to trouble you again
No
What are you looking at inside?
I don't know. I don't know where to look.
You two are really amazing
I think after she rejected me
I just feel really good
I really think it will be very relaxing
I am very relaxed
We have a lot of actions
Still like children
But actually
When handling many things
Indeed already
Yes
Sit up straight
Guo Guo (Ren Jiabi) is running away
What am I doing?
Street Punk No. 2
Street Punk
I don't even know what's going on
So heavy
Too much information
That part we just watched
was the quietest moment
Immersed
Speechless
Let's go through the timeline.
I knocked on the door.
But I actually knocked on two boys' doors.
Yes.
Old Su and Yunting.
Then Yunting.
We had a one-on-one date.
Then with Old Su.
Only on the first day.
That brief one-hour meeting.
Then I thought.
This time I want to create an opportunity.
To understand the other boy I have doubts about.
I want to get to know him.
After having one-on-one with me.
My own feelings.
Then I will make a judgment.
Yes.
I was also afraid of not knocking on Hu Yunting's door.
I don't know if it's guilt or something else.
I can't let it go.
So I said.
I honestly told him.
I believe the boy I'm interested in.
He should be able to understand.
You were very brave to directly tell me.
It feels much better this way.
I can understand what you're thinking.
And will support you.
I hope you can.
Find the answers you need.
By doing this.
You didn't hurt anyone.
You also respected your own feelings.
That's very good.
Behind Kaka (Zheng Weiying)
You can tell just by knocking on the door
Actually, there was hesitation
Right?
But you went to knock on Hou Chengjie’s door
Sometimes I
Hope I can take care of everyone
Actually
But after he rejected me
I really breathed a sigh of relief
I am very grateful to Xiao Hou
He allowed me at this point
I started anew
If I am interested in you later
I will invite you again
Or something like that
But my knocking on the door at that moment
It was not pure
But my Brother Hou
We were just talking about
Life and death situation
How dare you
I think posture is still important
Eating manners are still important
Table manners are very important.
Yes.
I think these two approaches
actually each have their own merits.
He doesn't have any so-called
opportunistic behavior.
So in the end, you must discuss it.
If you don't discuss it, I will...
You really are...
You talk about others like Luo Junfan.
I need to point something out to you now.
What's wrong with you?
Okay, I'll talk about this matter.
I think
from my perspective,
when considering these things.
But in a relationship,
it's especially not like this.
You should speak directly.
Actually, you should just say it directly.
No.
I think the past few days
we did get along well.
But
I found someone I'm more interested in.
So now I can't.
I can't.
It might be better to say it this way.
Because Xia Xia (Xia Mengting) used a word
called "confused."
Yes.
She doesn't understand.
So I think
this is where I'm particularly timid.
Considering
we still have to stay here for more than twenty days,
how should we get along?
Maybe we should avoid it for now.
It will be better.
But actually, this is
wasting time.
Maybe I'm still considering too much.
So I think
this is not right.
You think so much, consider so much,
you should actually express
your true thoughts.
This is a greater respect for others.
Surfing
Indoor surfing
So cool
So beautiful
This
Your eyes
Houzi (Hou Chengjie)
It hurts
No
Guozi (Ren Jiabi)'s expressions are all very funny
I want her emoji pack
Hou (Chengjie)
Little Hou makes people feel very secure
Do you know?
Sweet
You are bold and meticulous
Playing with water guns at the end, right?
This is pretty good too
I want to be that little water gun
watching you fall in love
Look, Old Hou's speaking speed has increased
He's relaxed
It's me
Swing dance
Come, let me investigate
My brother
My brother's idol burden
My brother has great jumping ability
He's taking off
No need for that, brother
Don't do that
Some "dead" memories
My brother's expression
He straightened his chest and lifted his head
Don't play it again
Brother, lower the corners of your mouth
My brother is so shy, like a young boy
His hands are trembling
You look like you're wearing the same clothes as today
Don't speak
Really beautiful
Looks like he's in his twenties
So young
My brother really
Ms. Ka (Zheng Weiying), you really know how to guide
You made my brother
Suddenly change from a reserved state to this
I think only you
can make Brother Chen so happy
In this environment
Sunset
We can see the sunset again
I, Tian (Liang Tian)
No problem
I told you
It's the wind (blowing)
It really is the wind
Okay
Very beautiful
What is this blinking thing?
Are you filming a short video?
Beef noodles
It's very delicious
I'm sorry
This shot
What is this
Who edited this
What is this thing
What's wrong with you guys
This
This visual effect
You guys are causing trouble
But his beef noodles
are really complicated to make
He put a lot of effort into making them
Eat less, teacher
Save me a bite
He didn't tell me it was made for you
How would I know
I still want to eat
Now I know
You are so supportive
Wait a moment
I'm sorry
I love you
I apologize
I thought this was the way to show it tastes good
I'm sorry
I apologize to you
So annoying
I still need to take it back for a late-night snack
Yes
That one is also not very perceptive
I
I'm not angry
Not that angry
Not really angry
Just speechless
It's okay
Really, it's okay
His hand
It's fine
Now Liang Tian knows
I have a question, Hu Yunting
Why didn't you say anything?
I mean, I want to keep a bowl
I was thinking of making a big pot
No matter what, there will be leftovers
Another part of me wants to say
Then make more
A steaming bowl is fine too
And at that stage
Everyone must have been puzzled by me
Everyone didn't really know how I felt
So I didn't want
To let everyone know what I was thinking too quickly
Why don't you want everyone to know
What you're thinking
Part of it is
I don't want to be influenced by everyone's voices
Their comments influenced me
And another part
Is gradually seeing
Some people are interested in you too
So I don't want to affect them
And I don't want to be affected by them
Yes
What's wrong?
This shot
What are you doing?
Here it comes
I have a very deep impression of this
Really deep
With whom?
Why are you looking at me?
Do you know?
At that moment, I also thought it was you
Look at me
Such deep affection in this gaze
You know, a tough guy's tenderness is really
irresistible
Guozi (Ren Jiabi)
So brave
So sweet
That's great
This melon is so sweet
Teacher
It's so beautiful
Why is it so beautiful
Ask yourself why it's so beautiful
Because the most beautiful one is you, Teacher
But I'm very curious
You are very emotional and charge forward
Wowo (Ren Jiabi) is very rational
A person who moves forward step by step
When you find yourself so passionate
And the other person is a bit rational
Your feeling is
When we invest our emotions
We all hope to get feedback from the other person
This is certain
So if I feel it
There will be a bit of frustration
But it won't stop me from moving forward
Understood
I think the cute thing about Xiao Hou is
He does many small things quietly
You see her afraid of going into the water
You will encourage first
Then you find that she tried
You won't continue to force
You handle it very well
Xiao Hou's kind of
Is a very passionate and direct love
If you ask everyone
Do you long for
Having this kind of passionate and direct love
For me, it's fifty-fifty
I think it depends on the person
If the other person
is someone I also have feelings for
then his directness and passion
can directly lead to a result
which is being together
But if the other person
is someone I don't find attractive
or have no feelings for
then his directness and passion
will also bring me pressure
I might feel a bit scared
and part of it is
because of my own insecurities
and another part is that
I need to get to know someone slowly
and take things step by step
So I'm not saying Xiao Hou is bad
I actually admire him
and hope to learn from you
not to overthink or think too far ahead
take it step by step
because you gave her this
and she can accept it
so this is very good
Wowo (Ren Jiabi) is using her way
to embrace this passion and directness
If everyone were to record again
Regarding what happened today,
these events and actions,
will you change?
Will your mood change?
Old Luo (Luo Junfan)
My main line won't change.
The main line won't change.
But from you,
I have learned many better ways and methods.
My methods have many inappropriate aspects.
So I will take this as
future experience to improve.
I also want to be a good person.
I will re-record it again.
I think my approach and feelings
will not change.
But after seeing this,
it will make me change my view of Brother Chen (Zhang Chenxi).
Actually, Brother Chen (Zhang Chenxi) relatively speaking,
he also gave me a lot of emotional value.
Because this interaction is definitely mutual.
When I reach out to pull him,
he must catch my hand.
So I am also very grateful to him.
Regarding the beef noodles incident
We are back to this again
But I also want to say
There is actually a better way
For example, if the first bowl
I would have taken a bowl and set it aside
Like Xia Xia (Xia Mengting) did, take it to the room
Actually, I learned this too
So there is such a trick, did you know?
A trick
The way you learned the technique seems different
Hers is deeper, more profound
If I had another chance
I would be willing to try
To take better care of my own feelings
And respect my feelings at that moment
Say whatever I want to say
Life in the small house is really
quite unique
especially after we watched today
including us now
everyone has upgraded
including Lao Luo (Luo Junfan)
in future life
will definitely do very well
so I really look forward to
recording again
each of us can do better
and I am very grateful to everyone for joining us
for today's third episode of the watch-along recording
thank you all for liking
our "Half-Mature Lovers" Season 4
today's watch-along ends here
please continue to support us
bye-bye